(Sheldon:)After the nightmare
of Anything Can Happen Thursday...
(Sheldon:)...this is Friday night
the way it was meant to be.
(Howard:)Who's up for Sheldon-Free Saturday?
(Penny:)Oh, hey, guys.
Hey, Penny and Stuart.
(Leonard:)Hey, Stuart.
(Penny:)- Hey, guys.
- So, what are you kids up to?
(Penny:)Stuart has a piece in an art show
that's opening tonight.
(Leonard:)And you guys are going together. Great.
(Stuart:)It is great. Really great.
It's freaking awesome.
- What are you doing?
- Friday night.
(Penny:)That means Chinese food
and vintage video games?
(Sheldon:)Vintage doesn't even begin to describe
what we have planned.
(Sheldon:)Tonight we are playing the classic 1980
interactive text adventure, "Zork."
(Sheldon:)It's the buggy beta version.
Wow, "Zork."
(Penny:)- Well, you guys have fun.
- Yeah.
STUART: See you, guys.
- See you, Stuart.
- Hey, Howard?
- Yes?
(Leonard:)Take me to a bar with women.